enstage.com 2014-03-01

# enStage - Privacy policy

enStage is committed to protecting your privacy.  We have adopted privacy principles which are addressed in the following sections.

Type of information collected on enStage.com

**Personal Information**  
Personal information is information that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, mailing address, email address, etc. Personal information is only obtained when you voluntarily provide the information to us. enStage uses personal information to better understand your needs and interests and to provide you with better service. 

Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured it will be used only for the intent it was collected for. 

**Non-Personal Information**  
Non-Personal information is information that does not identify you as an individual, such as your browser type, IP Address, the URL of the previous web site you visited, etc. enStage may automatically collect certain types of non-personal information from you when visiting enStage.com. This helps us understand the usage of our site and demographics of our visitors.

External links  
  
enStage website (enStage.com) may at times link to external websites.  enStage is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those sites. 

#### Acceptance of policy 

By visiting enStage.com, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and we have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time and will post any changes on this page..

This Privacy Policy applies only with respect to the information that we collect on enStage.com. 

**enStage respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting your personal information that you share with us.**
